[rock music playing]
[breathing heavily]
Eui-ju!
CHAPTER 26:
YOU'RE AN OUTLIER
Damn it! [grunts]
[Eui-ju groaning]
[doctor] Hi there. How are you doing?
-[nurse] Who's the patient's guardian?
-Yes, that's me.
And how long has the patient
been sweating?
About 30 minutes.
Does the patient have a history
of stomach pain?
-I'm sorry. I don't know.
-Okay, you don't know.
Please go ahead
and wait in the waiting room.
Well, is it serious?
-Please just wait out there.
-Okay.
Okay, we have an emergency!
Okay. Let's check your stomach.
-It hurts. Yeah.
-It hurts?
-Let me press here this time.
-It really hurts.
Let's transfer her to the ER now.
We're transferring her to the ER.
EMERGENCY ROOM
ENTRY RESTRICTIONS
We're moving her now.
[tense music playing]
[breathes heavily]
Oh, boy. If they're taking her there,
it's one of two things.
This is not good.
Not good at all.
[clicks tongue]
It's not good?
HANA UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTER
She's going to be okay, right?
Well…
[nurse] Is Yeo Eui-ju's guardian here?
Yes, here.
Mr. Ga.
Mr. Ga, what do I do?
[sobbing] I knew something was off.
I haven't had an appetite,
and my stomach's been acting up.
I saw this on TV recently.
Acute leukemia.
The program said that
even healthy people can get it.
And if you collapse out of nowhere,
it means it's already late-stage.
I'm only…
[sobbing] I'm only 18 years old.
I was gonna start
buying R-rated novels myself,
load up like $70 in credits
and just binge.
[sobbing continues]
-Mr. Ga.
-[Woo-su sighs]
I…
I don't have a good feeling about this.
I-I think that I…
[doctor] How are you feeling?
What's wrong with her, Doctor?
-Doctor.
-Okay.
Now, please take a look
at this scan, dear.
Okay. This right here indicates that
it was progressing for quite a while.
Your condition was very, very poor.
-You should've come in a lot sooner.
-[whimpers]
Mr. Ga, what do I do?
I don't know what to do…
[sighs]
It's okay. I'm sure it's nothing serious.
Mr. Ga. I don't want to die.
-It's all right. Don't cry, okay?
-What do I do?
-You're gonna be okay.
-Please call my mom for me.
[Woo-su] If you get treated,
you'll be fine!
My mom, I want to see my mom.
Is it really serious?
It's constipation.
Huh?
[stammering] I don't understand.
Can someone be constipated enough
to pass out?
Wouldn't she need some more tests?
It was completely packed inside.
Everything white you see in here is stool.
We gave her an enema.
And this is how it looks now.
All cleared up. You see?
Oh. And once you get home,
you should weigh yourself too.
You're good to leave now.
[whimpers]
Mr. Ga, you can just leave without me.
I can… I can go back home on my own.
Please don't say anything and just leave.
Please.
Oh, why aren't you leaving?
Hurry up and leave. Please go.
Please go.
I don't understand.
How do you
always…
How do you always manage to disappoint?
Goodbye.
[whimpers]
Should I just transfer schools?
Oh. Over there.
-Eui-ju!
-[groaning]
-[Shin] Eui-ju! Eui-ju!
-Where is Eui-ju?
-Eui-ju!
-Oh, sweetheart! Oh, Eui-ju!
-My goodness, Eui-ju! Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-What is it?
-I'm okay. I'm all right.
-Mom, I want to transfer.
-Transfer?
EPISODE 8
-Mmm.
-[sighs]
I wonder what made him change his mind
about the shoot.
I bet he was blackmailed.
Yeah. You guys don't know
how scary the principal is.
Her face changes in a second.
But Woo-su isn't one to be blackmailed.
-You're right.
-Right.
-Yeah.
[sighs] But what could
she have on him, then?
[keypad beeping]
-He's here. Make sure you apologize.
-[door opens]
Fine, I will.
You're late. You haven't had dinner yet?
[clears throat]
I'll get you some rice. Get him some soup.
Good job today.
That's all, really?
I thought you said
you had something to tell Woo-su.
Sorry about earlier.
What are you sorry for?
I said sorry. Isn't that enough?
I mean…
[sighs]
I'm sorry for filming you,
even though I know you hate it…
and also for telling you to get over it.
Then that's enough.
Spoon?
Oh. Right. The spoon.
[chuckles] How cool.
[chuckles]
Don't you have something to say?
I won't call you a fruit bat
for the next month.
How about the rest of your life?
-You wish.
-You sure can, four eyes!
-[grunts] You fruit bat.
-What?
-What? You heard him! Fruit bat.
-[laughs]
He said it. Yeah.
And he said he wouldn't!
I didn't promise you yet.
[both laughing]
I'm not eating.
-This is just stupid!
-Don't eat it, then.
[sobs]
[sighs]
I thought I was finally done
embarrassing myself.
[sobbing continues]
Eui-ju! Damn it.
[Eui-ju] It was strong.
It was warm
and really cozy.
[heartbeat thumping]
[gasps]
Oh.
[groans, sniffles]
[sighs]
The current state of constipation.
According to research
amongst high school students,
and the study of respective causes,
the top three factors are:
lack of exercise at 43%,
fast food at 24.6%,
and irregular sleep at 16%.
I believe we ended up
with yesterday's disaster
because you dismissed every single one.
I'll keep that in mind.
And thank you for yesterday.
I'm not religious or anything like that.
But it felt weird, showing you mercy
when you stabbed me in the back.
How constipated were you that
you had to go to the ER?
That's because
you didn't drink enough water.
Your poop was so hard that
it was stuck in there.
[stammers] No, that's not true.
[Yoon] Are you okay, Eui-ju?
I heard you had to go to the ER.
[sighs] I can't believe you let it stay
in there until it became that bad.
-You're definitely a bit slow.
-Uh…
-Ah. Good job yesterday.
-Wait, Mr. Noh.
What was that yesterday?
You said you knew about it.
Knew what?
You said you knew all about my secret.
I don't know anything.
[gasps]
Your face has really cleared up.
You look great now.
[door closes]
What the…
Did I fall for his lie?
So, Math didn't tell him about my novel?
At all?
Hey, Eui-ju! Going to the ER
for constipation is no big deal!
Don't be so embarrassed!
Hey, I wish you a clean finish!
Good luck, Eui-ju!
Constipation is no joke!
Okay, I'll stop. See you!
[sobs]
-Oh A-rin.
-Here.
CHAPTER 27:
LIKE A CAT, LITTLE BY LITTLE
-Choi Yu-mi.
-Here.
-Yeo Eui-ju.
-Choi Go-ya.
-Here.
Choi Ji-a.
-Hong Su-min.
-Here.
-Jeon Chae-won.
-Im Su-yeon.
-Here.
-Jenny.
Have fun with your classes today.
Good luck.
[students] Thank you.
Yeo Eui-ju, outside.
[door opens]
[students murmuring]
[sighs]
Why is Choi Ji-a not here?
I'm not really sure either.
[sighs]
When I asked about her
on my first day at this school,
you were the only one who answered me.
Guess what that means.
Right.
I thought maybe you could help Choi Ji-a
adjust to the school,
maybe help her change a little.
That's the reason I talked to you
and the reason I trusted you.
So take more interest
and try to help a out a little more.
Imagine someone waiting for you at school,
you'll force yourself to attend.
Even if you don't want to,
don't you think?
[gasps]
But Mr. Ga,
the way I see it, it's not good
to go too fast with Ji-a.
You need to be gentle
and take it slow
like with a cat little by little.
Then do that.
-Four demerit points today.
-[gasps]
Will you betray my trust again?
I won't, Mr. Ga.
[sighs, mumbling]
[grunts]
Darn Choi Ji-a.
Ji-a's not here again.
I know.
And do you know why she's always alone?
I don't know.
Well, some people find it more comfortable
to be alone. Maybe she's like that.
Mmm… Honestly, Ji-a is a bit scary.
If I rub her the wrong way,
she might blow up.
[chuckles]
Nah. She's not that scary.
She's just quiet.
She was in my class
in our first year of high school.
Whenever there was chalk on the floor,
she would put it right back on the board.
Oh, and while everyone else hated
taking out the recycled waste,
she'd stay until the very end
to finish it all by herself.
-Mmm…
-So then… [sharply inhales]
…her actions speak louder than her words.
I think that's just her style.
Mm-hmm.
Ji-a's here.
Oh.
You're here.
You should've been on time.
Why were you late today, Ji-a?
[Jenny] Mmm…
[bell rings]
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
-Hi.
-[students] Hello.
All right, turn to page 280.
[students] Okay.
Oh.
Everyone.
We'll be holding a poetry and art
exhibition to celebrate Literature Month.
Each class needs
to pick one representative.
Is there anyone who wants to write a poem?
Mr. Yoon! Eui-ju.
She's really good at writing.
Right, she always doodles in her notebook.
She even won a contest last year.
-[students] Ooh.
-[chuckles]
Oh, really? In that case, it'll be nice
if Eui-ju can be the class representative.
What do you say, Eui-ju?
Sure. I'll give it a try.
Mr. Yoon. Can Go-ya do the drawings?
Yeah, sounds great.
So, Go-ya. Can you do it?
Yes. Anything I can do to help.
Okay then. You both are
the representatives for Class 2.
[both giggle]
I'm excited.
-Okay. We'll do our best.
-Okay.
[giggling]
Are you cleaning because of your demerits?
Uh… [chuckles] Yes.
I don't know when I'll get more
so I need to cross them out while I can.
Did you have lunch already?
Yes, did you?
I did.
Eui-ju.
Yes?
Mr. Ga knows that you weren't filming
when you were out with your phone
when we first met.
Really?
Mmm.
Then why is he always picking on me?
Oh.
It's because of the glasses.
The glasses?
[sighs]
Yes. His glasses.
I was the one who had them
when he couldn't find them anywhere.
You were the one who had his glasses?
Yes.
Didn't Mr. Ga tell you?
He didn't say a word about it.
[Eui-ju] What the…
He didn't talk crap about me
for throwing his glasses away?
Anyway, he's not like that
because he has hard feelings against you.
So don't get too upset.
[chuckles] Okay.
Thank you so much for your concern.
Oh. By the way, it's truly incredible that
you made your literary debut.
Nah, it's nothing.
I've just enjoyed writing poetry
since I was little.
At first,
it was simply like writing a journal.
The emotions that were too heavy
to keep inside, I let out in my writing.
After failing the New Spring
Literary Contest so much,
I got lucky one day,
and was selected by a magazine.
Of course, I still kept doubting myself.
Was it the correct way to write?
But then, I kept writing.
And then I realized
it was about putting your heart into it.
Yeah. Actually,
I've been sort of writing novels as well.
Seriously?
That's cool.
Not at all.
[chuckles]
Sir, what should I do to be really good
at writing novels?
[sighs]
Every single character has to have
a voice of their own.
I think that's important.
Every single character has to have
a voice of their own…
-Right.
-Oh.
-Wow, Mr. Yoon. That's cool.
-[both chuckle]
I can't wait to read your piece
for the exhibition.
Ah…
You went to the store?
Yeah.
You should've come with me.
Thank you.
What did you do?
Huh? Ah, I had a talk with Mr. Yoon.
[sighs] Hey. He's really cool, you know?
Apparently, he wrote poetry
since he was in middle school.
He failed a known Literary Contest
until he made a debut
through a different route
unrelated to the contest.
You know what? I'll write something
really good for the exhibit.
That way your amazing drawings
will stand out even more.
Let's show everyone
your beautiful drawings…
[sighs] …and how fantastic they are.
Oh, I'm nervous.
[slurps]
Mmm.
Should I start with the title?
Wait, no. [inhales sharply]
CHAPTER 28: I'M GOING TO TRY
TO UNDERSTAND IRRATIONAL NUMBERS
FILES FOR MR. GA
REAL FILES
[sighs]
[smacks lips] Right.
FILES FOR MR. GA
[sighs]
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 5
[groans]
[sighs]
[whimpers, groans]
WOO-SUUUUUUUU
[sighs] No.
Just skip it. [sighs] No.
[clicks tongue] I'll come back to it.
No. No.
REAL FILES
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 5
[inhales deeply] Hmm.
[western music playing]
JUST THEN, SOMEONE GRABBED…
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 5
Why aren't you coming to my house?
YOON'S EYES WIDEN IN SURPRISE.
IT'S SI-ON
I can't go there anymore.
Actually, I won't.
You can't handle Discrete Math without me!
If I don't teach you,
you're just gonna fail.
I'll be fine.
I'll pay you.
What?
I know you need money.
I'll pay you if you come to my house.
Isn't that why
you go to Kang Tae-ha's house?
No, that's not it.
Yes, it is.
How am I any different from that punk?
Well, he just is.
He's different? How so?
In the end, he's still trying to buy you
with money. Isn't it the same?
[Tae-ha] Since you're poor,
you'll have to compensate me
with something other than money.
Six thousand.
I'll watch how you repay all of it.
[scoffs]
Fine, go ahead.
Get mad while you keep your pride.
You're gonna take the money anyway, right?
I'm curious.
How much is your pride really worth?
Why do you take it this far?
Why do you have to make me feel
this miserable?
Do I look that easy to you?
Don't waste your time.
Just think of a number.
Listen. You're going to regret it.
You're definitely going to regret it.
Oh, no.
I'll never regret it.
Not even if I die.
END OF EPISODE 5
[Eui-ju] "Save."
[sighs]
FILES FOR MR. GA
You can do this.
Eui-ju.
You can do it. [grunts]
I couldn't stop yawning.
I need to go to bed.
Right after dinner.
What are we having?
Uh… I don't know.
Something really crispy and warm.
-Ah… This jerk is way too picky.
-[Da-ju] Crispy!
Hey, we have some curry left.
-Curry?
-Yes. We have some left.
Go without me.
-Where are you going?
-The library.
He goes to the library a lot.
Hey, don't be late for dinner!
[Dong-ju] Is there anything in the library
worth reading for Woo-su, though?
[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 5
[Si-on] From now on,
I'm gonna be a piece of work,
just for Choi Yoon.
This isn't like you.
No?
EPISODE 5, FOR MR. GA
Then what is, huh?
I know you didn't even like me.
You're suddenly doing this
because I got close with Tae-ha.
Is that it? Are you jealous now?
Jealous?
You think I'm actually jealous?
[scoffs, laughs]
[funky music playing]
That's right, I am.
The way I treated you was all an act.
I didn't want you to see my true feelings.
But seeing Tae-ha by your side,
it drove me crazy.
[Yoon] It's no use now.
Snap out of it, Yoon!
You've got no one, but me.
There's no other choice.
Without me, you've got nothing.
You know that!
END OF EPISODE 5
What is it, Mr. Ga?
Do you not like it?
[sighs]
Huh?
[sighs] What was that?
I made him look like
a total obsessive guy.
What is he unhappy about?
Oh, boy.
There's still tape around his glasses.
What is it?
I'm just wondering
if you aren't going to get new glasses.
I ordered a new pair already.
I bet they're expensive.
I know I can't pay for your new glasses.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry, right?
Of course.
Is that your excuse for giving up on math?
Yes.
Write it the way you want to then.
What?
You can stick to your version,
instead of doing mine.
Are you serious?
No way. Can I really do that?
[sniffles]
Honestly, after you caught me
writing back then,
I actually thought it was all over.
I figured
I'd never be able to write again.
So, why are you even
letting me keep writing it?
To Pythagoras,
root two was something abnormal.
Huh?
That's random.
In those days, only natural numbers
were thought to be computable.
Anything that couldn't be expressed
as a fraction was considered irrational
and to be rejected.
It was an idea that shouldn't even exist.
Do you know what happened
to the Pythagoreans?
In the end, a student named Hippasus,
who discovered root two,
met a mysterious death.
They killed him because of that?
It's unclear who killed him.
It's just a rumor.
Dang. I guess Pythagoras
was a really scary man.
Irrational number.
Irrational number, right?
I believe it's worth embracing that which
isn't rational or logical for that matter.
I won't fall into the same trap
as Pythagoras
who rejected root two
because it didn't fit his logic.
Couldn't you make it a bit simpler?
I want to understand irrational numbers.
[light pop music playing]
[Eui-ju]
Fangirling used to be my only joy in life.
-Are you okay?
-But now,
every time he crosses my mind.
[grunts] I get so mad!
-I really don't want to think about him.
-Let's go.
I'm not supposed to think about him.
But he's stuck in my head.
[Go-ya] You're already head over heels
for him. But you're trying to deny it.
That's just typical.
Your words say otherwise, but your heart
is already racing toward him.
[Eui-ju] No! What? Oh, no.
I can't. I shouldn't like him.
I simply can't!
[Go-ya] Hey.
Mr. Jung's not your crush, is he?
They've gotten really close.